Sam, what are you doing?
Watching the news.
You're supposed to be upstairs
with us rehearsing for iCarly.
Why aren't you wearing
your 8os costume?
Why aren't you more appealing?
Let's go.
Wait, just lemme watch
this next story.
I think it's about bigfoot.
No one cares... bigfoot?
Why are you all interested in...?
Shhhhh!
On the northern outskirts of
mount bakeratational forest,
two hikers saw something
that, at first,
they thought was a large bear.
It's bigfoot.
I know it's bigfoot.
Shhh!
You were the only one talking.
Shhhhh!
Now, before you dismiss this
sighting as another bigfoot hoax,
take a look at this footage
shot by one of the hikers
with his mobile phone.
There.
See that?
Bigfoot.
Could it just been a guy in a costume.
Maybe you're just a guy in a costume.
Actually, I am.
Hush.
So, was it a hoax?
No.
Or was it bigfoot?
Yes.
Discussion over.
Take that, Mrs. Guntrell.
Our fifth grade teacher?
Yeah, don't you remember?
We all had to write a report
about a rare creature?
Oh, yeah.
I wrote mine about that tall
pygmy that dated my mom.
Tall pygmy?
They're very rare.
Well, I wrote my report
on bigfoot and I worked
really hard on it.
And then Mrs.
Guntrell was all, "bigfoot isn't real,
so you get an 'f'."
I'd like to give her an "f".
Aah, Ahh.
Hey, you guys.
Wow, that's a pretty sexy dance there.
It's not a dance.
I went swimming at Socko's today
and I got water in my ear.
Uh, what up with the 8os garb?
These are costumes for an
iCarly bit we were rehearsing.
Till carly saw a bigfoot story
on the news and went all
weee-ooo-wooo-dee-wooo-wooo.
You saw the bigfoot video on the news.
People fake chiz like
that all the time.
Ah, is this about the "f"
you got from Mrs. Guntrell?
Maybe.
Kid, there's no such thing as bigfoot.
Bop.
Oh, but there is such a
thing as the beavecoon?
Yes, there sure is.
What's a beavecoon?
A creature that lives in
Spencer's diseased imagination.
I saw one with my own eyes.
Don't tell the story.
I was in the eight grade.
Ohhh.
My body was just starting to change...
Ohhh coach berferd took
our whole class on a field
trip to the peckinpah trail.
And just as dusk fell, I saw it.
What?
A beavecoon, a creature about
yay wide and yay long.
Yay?
It had the head of a beaver
and the body of a raccoon.
The beavecoon.
Yes, and it looked at me and went...
There's no such thing
as a beavecoon.
Is to.
There's no such thing as bigfoot.
Then there's no such
thing as tall pygmies.
You wanna see the videos
of my mom and gwooji?
Not at all.
No way.
Are we gonna rehearse this or what?
In 5...4...3...2...
♫ I know, you see ♫
♫ somehow the world ♫
♫ will change for me ♫
♫ and be so wonderful ♫
♫ live life, breathe air ♫
♫ I know somehow ♫
♫ we're gonna get there ♫
♫ and feel so wonderful ♫
♫ it's all for real ♫
♫ I'm tliling you ♫
♫ just how I feel ♫
♫ so wake up the members ♫
♫ of my nation ♫
♫ it's your time to be ♫
♫ there's no chance ♫
♫ unless you take one ♫
♫ and the time to see ♫
♫ the brighter side ♫
♫ of every situation ♫
♫ some things are meant to be ♫
♫ so give it your best ♫
♫ and leave the rest to me ♫
♫ leave it all to me ♫
♫ just leave it all to me ♫
Sync by Hana.Bean
www.Addic7ed.Com
hey.
Man, how long should a crock
pot take to cook gumbo?
How would I know?
Well, check it on your pear phone.
There's no crock pot app.
Man, everybody's talking about
bigfoot because of that video
on the news.
I know.
During my last class, the... hey, hey.
What?
Will you guys tell Shawn
that bigfoot does exist?
Will you guys tell Gibby
that bigfoot is a myth?
Well, myth doesn't ne... told ya.
There's no such thing as a bigfoot.
You watch your mouth.
What?
Or I will watch it for you.
For me?
Bigfoot does exist.
This is just like the
last time with unicorns.
There's no bigfoot.
Guys, don't fight about it.
Ah, let 'em fight.
The only fun part about
this whole bigfoot debate
is watching people
scream at each other.
People screaming at
each other isn't fun.
Yeah, it is.
Watch this.
Isn't that miss Briggs' bullhorn?
It was before I took it.
Attention, attention, people.
Okay, everybody who thinks
bigfoot is real, say "yeah."
Yeah.
Okay, now everyone who thinks
bigfoot is fake, say "yeah."
Yeah.
Okay, about half and half.
That means half of you
are stupid, discuss.
Stupid.
Hey, you guys, guess what.
What's up?
Why is everyone fighting?
The bigfoot debate.
Oh, good.
Gimme that.
Hey, I wanna speak to everyone.
You guys.
Everyone.
Listen.
If you wanna know the
truth about bigfoot,
watch iCarly tomorrow
night because Sam and I
will be interviewing
doctor Sydney Van Gurbin.
Who's that?
We don't know who that is.
He is a scientist who's
been researching bigfoot
for the last 10 years.
He even wrote this book:
Bigfoot true or real?
Bigfoot.
So watch iCarly.
How'd you get that guy
to come on iCarly?
I just e-mailed him and he
wrote back saying he'd do it.
We're really gonna talk
about bigfoot on iCarly?
Sure, why not?
You don't think we'd kinda
be jumpin' the shark
a little bit with that?
No.
Lots of people are really curious
about... hey, hey, hey, hey.
Get to class.
Go.
Scurry.
Scoot.
Come on, let's go.
So you took my bullhorn.
No.
No, no, no.
See Sam was the one... come with me.
Loud.
And finally, a hearty
layer of Mozzarella...
There's no such thing
as too much cheese.
Eeee.
Oh, the cheese.
Oh.
Raining cheese deliciousness.
And there.
That's how you make...
Gibby Parmesan.
Yay.
Gibby.
Now, that's Italian.
Ugh.
Augh.
Okay, this past week, all over America...
...Especially here
in Seattle... ...
People have been talking about one thing...
Or as bigfoot's called in Mexico...
So now we're gonna
bring out a scientist who's
possibly the world's
number one expert on bigfoot.
Sit down there.
So, thanks for being
here, doctor Van Gurbin.
Well, thank you for having me on.
No prob.
I know that lots of people
think bigfoot is a myth,
but that's just because they
haven't read my new book:
Bigfoot: True or real?
Right.
So, what'd you think about the recent
bigfoot sighting by those hikers
in mount Baker national forest?
Do you think it was real?
Oh, I do.
In fact, two years ago I predicted
that bigfoot would be spotted
in that very location,
anbecause bigfoot usually
comes out of hibernation
during this time of the year.
You weren't popular
as a kid, were you?
No.
Sam.
So when's the first
time you... Spencer?
Uh... sorry, Spencer just
walked in for some reason.
Hi, sorry to interrupt.
Not sorry enough to not do it.
Ha.
Anyway, doctor Van Gurbin,
a question, if I may.
Uh, sure.
What do you know about the beavecoon?
Oh, my God.
Dude.
>. Surely you've heard of it.
It has the head of a beaver
and the body of a raccoon?
Is this person supposed to be here?
He's my brother.
Oh.
Well, I'm sorry, but I am not
familiar with a beavecoon.
But you're not denying that it exists.
And now, Sam and I will
sing a little song called
"Spencer's leaving."
♫ Spencer's leaving ♫
♫ it's time for you to go ♫
♫ so he's leaving ♫
♫ he's leaving ♫
♫ it's time for you to go away ♫
that song's lame.
Sorry about the intrusion.
Back to bigfoot.
Right.
So over the next few days,
I'll be camping out
in the northern outskirts of
mount Baker national forest.
To get some hard evidence on bigfoot?
Hahat's the dream.
And you can read about
that dream in my new book:
Bigfoot: True or real?
If you see an animal that looks
like this, please contact...
Aw, man.
Spencer.
Don't zoom in on it.
Ha, listen to this.
Since 2005, at least 56 people
claim to have seen bigfoot
in or around the northern areas
of mount Baker national forest.
Sure, 56 freaks and liars.
No, it says one was a girl
scout and one was a rabbi.
So a lying little girl
and a freaky rabbi.
I once met a freaky rabbi in Vegas.
Hey, can I have this root beer?
Wait, I think that's our last one.
It is, thanks.
Ah.
Look, it says right here:
Two graduate students from
the university of Fresno
recorded video of a female
beaver and a male raccoon
"socializing" by a River.
Ulch, this is diet.
Have you guys ever watched this show:
Celebrities underwater?
Oh, check this out.
In the past year,
tourists have reported
nearly a dozen sightings of
bigfoot in the wooded area
behind a well-known hot dog
stand called Robin's weiners.
I've heard of that place.
The food channel did a whole
thing about Robin's weiners
on American meats.
Here, click on the link.
Man, how can David schwimmer
hold his breath this long?
Wait, he's not moving.
> A-ha.
In the 1800s, a cherokee
Indian was bitten
by an animal he described
as having "head of beaver"
and "rump of raccoon."
He's still not moving.
Ryan seacrest said, "best
hot dog I ever had."
So?
Ryan seacrest is never wrong.
I guess there's never gonna
be a friends reunion.
Okay, look.
I wanna prove that bigfoot exists.
You wanna find a beavecoon,
and Sam wants to go
to Robin's weiners.
I do.
And?
Doesn't Socko have an R.V.?
You mean a recreational vehicle?
Yes.
He does.
So borrow it, and let's go up
to mount Baker national forest.
You wanna?
Yeah, c'mon.
Robin's weiners.
Let's do it.
Road trip.
I'm in.
Yeah.
Wow.
Oo.
Yes.
Yeah.
Awesome hot dog.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah.
Honking for Robin's weiners.
Robin's weiners.
Wow.
Oh, there's the exit.
Mount Baker national forest.
Right there, go, go.
I see it.
Oh, water in my ear.
Careful, careful.
Open your eyes.
Yeah.
And welcome to mount
Baker national forest.
Wow.
Yay, let's go find bigfoot.
And a beavecoon.
Bigfoot is our priority.
Nyeeehhh.
I'll set up the equipment.
Sam.
Sam?
Aw, she fell asleep while
eating one of Robin's weiners.
Sam, wake up.
Wow, it's nice out here.
Ah, I still got water in my ear.
Aa-aah.
Quit spazzing out.
You're gonna scare bigfoot away.
I don't think a seven-foot
beast man is gonna be afraid
of a 160-pound spazzy artist.
Okay, I'm gonna go set
these up in a tree.
What are those?
Motion-activated night-vision
wireless cameras.
Ahhhhh?
See, I set these up in a tall tree,
and when they pick up motion,
they turn on and transmit
an audio-video signal,
scanning a radius of up to 10 yards.
Ow, it hurts.
What?
The sound of him talking.
Look Sam, I'm not just gonna
stand here... just go set up
your tree cameras.
Okay.
All right.
There's a big tree.
I'm gonna go rig up my rope trap.
Wait, wait.
You're gonna try to trap bigfoot?
No, but there might be wild
pigs or deer in these woods.
I'm gonna trap a snack.
Here.
I need you to stick this in my head.
Why'd you bring this?
'Cause I read online that you
can use them to get water out
of a person's ear.
Try it.
You want me to use a Turkey baster
to suck water out of your ear?
Yeah, come on.
Put it in there.
Squeeze the thing on the end.
I kw what to squeeze.
Aha, it tickles my brain.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey.
What, what happened?
I was up in a tree and
I heard rustling,
and someone or some thing
was in... you think
it could've been bigfoot...?
...Or beavecoon?
Is that a Turkey baster?
Shh, listen.
Rustling.
Anybody see anything?
There.
Aaah.
Aw, it's just two guys.
And they're not even cute.
Bummer.
Hey.
How are you guys?
What are you guys doing here?
Looking for bigfoot.
Duh.
You see anything yet?
Perhaps a creature, yay wide,
yay long, head of a beaver,
body of a raccoon, sounds like...?
Aah.
Jeez.
Look, if you guys wanna find
bigfoot, go look somewhere else.
This is our spot.
You can't make us leave.
Whoa, bigfoot.
Where?
Aah.
Hey, did you just...?
Aah, Jeff I'm in trouble.
I really think you guys should go look
for bigfoot somewhere else.
I totally agree.
Aah.
..... ..... ..... ..... ..... ....
. ..... ..... ..... Excelle.
Yes, it's a fine weinery.
So any signs of bigfoot?
Not yet.
Me either, but I know he's out here.
Just like I wrote about
in my new book: Bigfoot...
We know about the book.
Well, happy searching.
He's an interesting man.
Yeah, I never knew a hot dog
place could be called a weinery.
I know.
Interasante.
My tree cameras, come on.
There.
I see something moving.
Awww, it's those idiot boys.
Look, tree cameras.
Let's take 'em.
Oh, no no, no, no, no.
Don't.
Awww, I got those for Christmas.
You see anything?
Just trees, and some bushes
and two squirrels wrestling.
Carly?
Hmm?
They're not wrestling.
Oh.
Sam's still asleep.
Yup, probably dreaming about
prancing through a field of hot dogs
and fried chicken legs.
Hey, you guys.
What are you wearing?
Camo.
I'm going out into the wilderness
to find me a beavecoon.
You mind wearing a special
camera on your helmet?
Well, I guess not.
All right, cool.
So I'll just take this and
just put that down there.
Careful.
Ah, come on, man up.
All right, so we angle that
down a little bit... ow.
... And then we stick this in your ear.
Okay.
All right.
Got it.
And now, we'll be able
to see whatever you see.
Did you see those squirrels?
Don't talk about it.
Ah.
Here beavecoons.
Come to Spencer, ya
lil freaks a'nature.
Tell him to look for bigfoot.
Spencer.
Aah, aah, aah, aah, aah.
Oh, hi.
Carly says, you should
look for bigfoot.
What was that?
My rope trap.
Hello?
Who's there?
Beavecoon?
Hey, aah, aah, oh God.
Ah, gah.
Get it off.
Get it off of me.
Ah, stop.
Stop.
Get off.
What are you?
Where are you?
What's happening?
Be careful.
Are his feet big?
Did we get bigfoot?
Not unless bigfoot has a
zipper running down his back.
Hah.
Eh.
Hey.
Doctor Van Gurbin?
Well, this is a scooby-doo moment.
I'm so sorry.
I... see my book wasn't selling
well, and my dad always told me
I'd be a failure.
Your dad was right.
So you dressed up like
bigfoot just to create hype?
Yes, so people would buy my new
book: Bigfoot I had that coming.
Ahhhh.
Guys.
What's wrong, Spencer?
What happened?
What is it?
I saw bigfoot and I ran away
'cause I didn't wanna be alone
in the woods all by
myself with bigfoot.
Aah.
Wait, you saw bigfoot in the woods?
Ye-aah.
Oh, get your camera.
Right.
You remember where you saw him?
Uh-huh.
Can you take us there?
Nuh-uhhh!
Yes.
Ready.
Guys, we gotta go.
Come on, Spencer.
See anything?
Hey, is this where you saw bigfoot?
Where'd Spencer go?
Duh, he climbed up that tree.
Spencer, what are you doing
at the top of that tree?
I'm very scared.
Come down from there.
Nahh.
I'll get him.
If bigfoot was here,
looks like he left.
Well, we're not giving up.
We're gonna stay here until... owwww!
What happened?
I got him out of the tree.
By throwing a rock at me.
At least the fall made the
water come out of my ear,
and some blood.
Wait, shh, listen.
What's that?
It sounded like the R.V.
You mean, our recreational vehicle?
Yes.
Who would've started our R.
V.?
Come on.
Move it, move it.
Let's get out.
Ahh.
Move it.
Come on, guys.
Ahhhh!
Where's the R.V.?
It's gone.
Look, what else is gone.
Doctor Van Gurbin.
That chunk a'chiz stole our R.
V.
Well, let's call the cops.
Yeah. I don't...
Our cell phones are in the R.V.
Well, how are we gonna get... hey.
Look, we got bigfoot.
Right here, baby.
Ugh, you guys are so stupid.
Why are these...?
Pull his head off.
Hey.
You're still trying to fool people?
I'm a sick person.
So, there's no real bigfoot?
Yeah, there is.
I just got into a fracas with him
in the woods 10 minutes ago.
Okay, wait.
If doctor Van Gurbin didn't steal our R.
V., then who did?
It's all right.
Come on people, let's
not be idiots here.
I mean, we're really
gonna stand around
thinking bigfoot stole our R.V.?
Sync by Hana.Bean
www.Addic7ed.Com
Repair and Synchronization by
Easy Subtitles Synchronizer 1.0.0.0